So many of you are asking that
in how much time does it take to receive the offer letter, so
first thing if you are
going through post program and your post program
is completed like your exam is also over,
your result is also out, then
you receive the offer letter after one week of the result, let's say
one week or
two weeks, you receive the offer letter
that you have to continue your job in this branch on this date, then
you receive it in one week,
if you are going through the course, if you are
going through placement then
you will get it very soon, if the
offer letter gets cancelled after the program then it
comes very late, it is not like that,
sometimes what happens is that you get a date, yes,
you have to join the branch, then
you get the offer letter
after one week, sometimes
you receive it a day before the job, the
time is late but if you have done placement
or  Then if you have done the course inside then you will get the
offer letter soon, so do not make a
big deal out of it, if your result has been declared and
your joining date has been declared then you should join,
your offer letter can come after joining or
even before joining, it
depends on the time.